<resources>
    <string name="app_name">app5</string>
    <string name="famous_restaurants">Famous Restaurants</string>
    <string name="tourist_attractions">Tourist Attractions</string>
    <string name="recommendations">\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tRecommendations</string>
    <string name="empty">"    "</string>
    <string name="one">It is a transmission tower located on Namsan Mountain in Seoul and a representative landmark of Seoul, and is a member of the World Tower Federation (WFGT).
The official name is Namsan Seoul Tower, and it is usually called Namsan Tower. It is often referred to as N Seoul Tower, the name of an observatory and complex cultural space that CJ Foodville leases and operates.
The old name was Seoul Tower (YTN Seoul Tower), and in December 2015, the name was changed to Namsan Seoul Tower when YTN opened Seoul Tower Plaza, a complex cultural space, on the lower floor of N Seoul Tower. The construction company for the facility is Hyundai EandC. source
The height of the tower itself is 236.7m, which is rather low compared to other landmark structures, but the total height of Namsan Mountain is 479.7m. Inside the building, two complex cultural spaces are operated for the general public: N Seoul Tower, which is leased and operated by CJ Foodville, and Seoul Tower Plaza, which is directly operated by YTN.</string>
    <string name="two">Gyeongbokgung Palace is the royal palace of the Joseon Dynasty located on Cheongwa-daero in Seoul, South Korea. It was founded in 1395, the 4th year of King Taejo, was burnt down in 1592 during the Japanese invasion of Korea in 1592, and rebuilt in 1868 under the leadership of Heungseon Daewongun. It was damaged during the Japanese colonial period and is currently undergoing a restoration project. It was built based on 《Jurye》 and Gogonggi. It is composed of 3 gates and 3 sets, each of which is outer, inner, and soft. Naejo is centered on Geunjeongjeon, and from outside the palace to Geunjeongjeon are Gwanghwamun, Heungnyemun, and Geunjeongmun.</string>
    <string name="three">The National Museum of Korea is a national museum located at 137 Seobinggo-ro, Yongsan-gu, Seoul, South Korea. It was launched on July 19, 1972, and the current museum was newly built and opened on October 28, 2005. The main building is divided into an east wing and a west wing, and consists of one basement floor and six floors above ground. The exhibition space is divided into three floors. With a length of 404 meters and a maximum height of 43.08 meters, it is the sixth largest museum in the world. There is a separate children museum and outdoor exhibition hall. It is closed on January 1st, and from May 1st, 2008, admission to the permanent exhibition hall and the Children Museum became free. Various performances are held at the affiliated theater Yong, and there are also affiliated facilities such as the traditional dye botanical garden and the Hangeul Museum. From November 13, 2017, the Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism installed a security checkpoint in front of the museum entrance for security reasons, allowing visitors to inspect and view the museum.</string>
    <string name="four">Exhibition hall and shopping mall in Jung-gu, Seoul. It was designed by British architect Zaha Hadid. According to the website, it is the world largest 3D atypical building. After Dongdaemun Stadium was demolished in 2007, it was built as part of the development policy for Dongdaemun Stadium. Currently, the operating institution is the Seoul Design Foundation, which is a funded institution by the Seoul Metropolitan Government, and it is in total management along with Dongdaemun History and Culture Park, which first opened in 2009.</string>
    <string name="five">Yeouido Saetgang Ecological Park is a park located in Yeouido-dong, Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul. In Saetgang Ecological Park, where reeds and water reeds grow thickly, there is a 6km trail, and you can learn about our native plants through information boards installed at 20-30m intervals. As Korea first ecological park, rare animals and plants such as the natural monument No. 323 kestrel, spot-billed ducks, herons, violets, horsetails, and willowfish live here. In order not to harm nature, the ecological park did not install benches, canteens, or streetlights for animals and plants to rest and sleep. It can be used all year round, but access to some sections is restricted during the breeding season of animals.</string>
    <string name="six">Gwangjang Market, which boasts a long history, is the first permanent traditional market in Korea with a tradition of over 120 years.
Representative examples are silk and cloth (hanbok), textile fabrics, women clothing, clothing subsidiary materials, import relief, mother-of-pearl lacquerware, needlework,
There are various foods, and the best and largest wholesale and retail market in Korea is formed.
Recently, it has been in the limelight as a filming location for news, dramas, and entertainment programs by famous domestic and foreign broadcasting companies and media outlets.
Currently, in conjunction with the Korea Tourism Organization, we are conducting a market tour commercialized as a tour course for foreigners.
We are making our country known worldwide.</string>
    <string name="notice">⦁ If you win, we will contact you by email and send you Seoul souvenirs to your address.</string>
    <string name="application">Application</string>
</resources>
